from Flickr. Go over to the right-hand side, grab Flickr from the list of options, drag it into the timeline, and put it where you'd like it to go, and it immediately goes out to Flickr and starts pulling in images based on the tags. Now, my developers really like ponies, and so they've set that as the default tag. Let's try something else, maybe something a bit more relevant to today. Now here are live images being pulled straight from the feed. If you come and watch this a week from now, this will be completely different, dynamic, just like the web, and just like the web, everything is sourced, so click your link, and you go straight to Flickr and see the source image. Everything you've seen today is built with the basic building blocks of the web: HTML, CSS and JavaScript. That means it's completely remixable. It also means there's no proprietary software. All you need is a web browser. So imagine if every video that we watched on the web worked like the web, completely remixable, linked to its source content, and interactive for everyone who views it. I think Popcorn could change the way that we tell stories on the web, and the way we understand the world we live in. Thank you. (Applause)
desde Flickr. Vayamos a la derecha, tomemos Flickr de la lista de opciones, arrastrémosla a la línea de tiempo y la colocamos donde deseamos; de inmediato vamos a Flickr y empieza a mostrar imágenes relacionadas a los tags. A mis desarrolladores les gustan los ponis, por eso lo han puesto como tag por defecto. Probemos algo diferente, quizá algo más relevante hoy. Son imágenes tomadas directamente desde la fuente. Si volvemos en una semana será completamente diferente, dinámico, como la web, exactamente como la web, todo tiene una fuente; si hacen clic en el enlace, van directo a Flickr y ven la imagen fuente. Todo lo que han visto hoy se construyó con los elementos básicos de la web: HTML, CSS y JavaScript. Significa que es totalmente remezclable. Significa también que no hay software propietario. Se necesita solo un navegador. Imaginen si todos los videos que miramos en la web funcionaran con la web, completamente remezclables, vinculados con sus fuentes, interactivos con todos los que los vieran. Creo que Popcorn podría cambiar nuestra forma de contar historias en la web y la forma de entender el mundo en el que vivimos. Gracias. (Aplausos)